You asked for it, scum!
Tu ai cerut-o, jigodie!
You lost - deal with it!
Ai pierdut - lasă-te păgubaș!
First day someone already pissed in my chest
Încă din prima zi, cineva s-a pișat la mine în cufăr
Two weeks ago some [...] stole my shoes
Acum două săptămâni, altcineva [...] mi-a furat încălțămintea
I looked for help, no mage heared me out
Am căutat ajutor, dar nimeni nu m-a ajutat
But I still have hope, that I'll be okay here
Da' încă mai sper că în bine se va fi schimbat
Igaraz with Agon - with them it's the worst
Igaraz și Agon - cu ei nu mă înțeleg mai deloc
I'll say, I'd rather live with a shadowbeast
Lasă-mă să-ți zic, mai bine aș sta cu bestia umbrei
The bell is ringing, I'll come back to the story later
Sună clopoțelul, revin mai târziu cu povestea
I don't want to be late to the summoning class
Nu vreau să întârzii la ora de convocare
Me and my golem - the two of us
Eu și cu golemul meu - noi doi
Nobody will bully me in the monastery anymore
Nu voi mai fi bătaia de joc a niciunuia
He'll help me, when they stand in our way
Golemul mă va ajuta când îmi vor sta în cale
Me and golem - the two of us
Eu și golemul - noi doi
Because for me he's more than a monster
Căci pentru mine el nu e doar un monstru
My choice, a friend, but summoned through a scroll
E alesul meu, prietenul meu, dar chemat printr-un pergament
Me and my golem - the two of us
Eu și golemul meu - noi doi
Nobody will bully me in the monastery anymore
Nie będzie gnębił mnie już nikt w klasztorze
He'll help me, when they stand in our way
Pomoże mi, gdy staną nam na drodze
Me and golem - the two of us
Eu și golemul - noi doi
Because for me he's more than a monster
Căci pentru mine el nu e doar un monstru
My choice, a friend, but summoned through a scroll
E alesul meu, prietenul meu, dar chemat printr-un pergament
My and my go...blin skeleton - not for me
Ja i mój go... blin, szkielet - to nie dla mnie
One shot puts down a wolf
Po jednym strzale padnie wilk
I have no other spells
Nie mam innych zaklęć
Noone has a golem scroll
Zwoju golema nie ma nikt
Again I'm on the bottom
Znowu jestem na dnie
I don't have the strength for anything anymore
Już mi na wszystko braknie sił
I don't know anymore, really
Nie wiem już, naprawdę
Although I have one thought in my head
Chociaż mam w głowie pewną myśl
Innos, eternal lord of light and fire.
Innosie, odwieczny panie światła i ognia
Bles...
Pobło...
Hey, you! What are you looking for over there?!
Ej, ty! Czego tam szukasz?!
Me and my golem - the two of us
Ja i mój golem - nas dwoje
Nobody will bully me in the monastery anymore
Nie będzie gnębił mnie już nikt w klasztorze
He'll help me, when they stand in our way
Pomoże mi, gdy staną nam na drodze
Me and golem - the two of us
Eu și golemul - noi doi
Because for me he's more than a monster
Căci pentru mine el nu e doar un monstru
My choice, a friend, but summoned through a scroll
Wyborem mym przyjaciel, lecz przywołany zwojem
Me and my golem - the two of us
Ja i mój golem - nas dwoje
Nobody will bully me in the monastery anymore
Nie będzie gnębił mnie już nikt w klasztorze
He'll help me, when they stand in our way
Pomoże mi, gdy staną nam na drodze
Me and golem - the two of us
Eu și golemul - noi doi
Because for me he's more than a monster
Căci pentru mine el nu e doar un monstru
My choice, a friend, but summoned through a scroll
Wyborem mym przyjaciel, lecz przywołany zwojem